Guide to the Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club scrapbook collection, 1974-2010
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club scrapbook collection
1974-2010
C0234
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections & Archives
5 linear feet (7 boxes)
The 12 scrapbooks document the club's activities and each scrapbook covers a range of years beginning in 1974. The collection is dated from 1974 to 2010 and is contained in 7 boxes.
Women's Club of Greater Reston (Reston, Va.)
Historical note
The Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club was founded in 1969 as a women's social organization. The Club's purpose is to extend a friendly, helping hand, to offer the opportunity to make new friends, find camaraderie, and enjoy a variety of creative, social, and recreational activities from September through June. The club currently meets under the name Women's Club of Greater Reston.
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia, and other planned communities.
Scope and Content
12 scrapbooks that contain newsclippings and photographs of the activities of the Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club. The collection is dated from 1974 to 2010 and is contained in 7 boxes.
The collection consists of scrapbooks from the Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club. Included in the scrapbooks are photographs, newsclippings, programs and other items from different years in the Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club's history.
Arrangement
Organized in one series chronologically.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Women's Club of Greater Reston on April 4, 2013.
Index Terms
Corporate Names:
Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club (Reston, Va.)
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Document Types:
Scrapbooks.
Contents List
- Greater Reston Newcomers and Neighbors Club scrapbook collection, 1974-2010
  - Scrapbook, 1974-1976 (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1981-1984 (Box 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1987-1989 (Box 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1989-1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1993-1994 (Box 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1995-1996 (Box 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1999-2001 (Box 7)
  - Scrapbook, 2001-2002 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 2009-2010 (Box 7)